Hey what have we done goa How are we
Oye qu hemos hecho vayaa Cómo estamos
tonight life do you want to run do you want to
noche la vida quieres correr quieres
run
correr
let's go if it's so
vamos si es tan
adorable crazy crazy crazy he's gone eh he's gone he's gone he's gone he's
adorable loco loco loco se le ha ido eh
gone look everything is
se le ha ido mira todo está
out of control No man But that's been No that's
descontrolado No hombre Pero eso sido No
been a fiddle no a fiddle that's what
eso sido un ficho no un fich se llamará
the song is called Well that's what I went to
así la canción Pues eso lo que he ido
check but I think no no
comprobar pero creo que no no
[ __ ] there will be please the jerks off it
madre gol habrá por favor las pajas
must have been something from the live show or what
hechas habrá sido algo del directo o qué
guys guys it's February and
chavales chavales estamos en febrero y
it's raining it's starting to fall a a little
está lloviendo está empezando a caer una
rain around here I mean it's
una una lluviecita por aquí o sea que
the Crazy World it's raining when it never
está el Mundo Loco llueve cuando nunca
rains this is mind-blowing and it's cold
llueve esto es flipante y hace frío
because we're at 25 grams which for this
porque estamos a 25 gr que para esta
time of year 25 grams at 1 in the afternoon
época del año 25 gr a la 1 de la tarde
Well the truth is it's cold but oh well it
Pues la verdad es que es frío pero bueno
is what it is guys it is what it is I've got
es lo que ha chavales es lo que hay me
three hairs growing on my eyebrows just so you
han salido tres pelos en las cejas que
know What's up guys Well I'm
lo sepáis Qué pasa chavales Bueno estoy
taking a walk today you know it's
dando una vuelta hoy ya sabéis que está
raining a little bit everything's wet
lloviendo un poquito está todo húmedo
it's very good  and this is one of the last
está muy bien y es una de las últimas
laps that I'm going to be taking around here
vueltas que me voy a ir pegando por aquí
in a while, let's see, there are going to be several
en en un tiempo a ver va a haber varios
changes in the sanctuary, you know
cambios en el santuario estamos sabéis
that we are involved in
que estamos metidos en en líos
legal trouble and in all kinds of trouble. Oh, and
judiciales y en líos de todo tipo Ah y
obviously there are going to have to be
obviamente va a haber que que hacer
changes, we have been preparing
cambios ya llevamos días preparándolo
everything for days in case we have to
todo en caso de que de que haya que
make drastic changes, okay, I'm not
hacer cambios drásticos de acuerdo Yo no
going to leave the animals alone, nor am I going
voy a dejar a los animales solos ni voy
to take the animals out of here, nor am I going to
a sacar a los animales de aquí ni voy a
do absolutely anything, so what we are
hacer absolutamente nada con lo cual lo
doing is preparing a
que estamos haciendo es preparar un
team of supervised people. Oh, there is going to
equipo de gente supervisada Ah va a
be a person who supervises them and
haber una persona que los supervise y
who is going to come here every week
que va a venir aquí todas las semanas
to see that everything is okay and there are going to be
para ver que está todo bien y va a haber
some people here who are going to be
aquí unas personas que van a estar Pues
feeding the animals, checking that
alimentando a los animales mirando que
everything is okay, if there is something that
esté todo bien si hay algo que se
needs watering, things like that. What a
necesita poner agua cosas así No qué
shame, what a shame, eh, the horse is behind
pena Qué pena eh tiene el caballo detrás
comes the mare and Hert doesn't like it, he doesn't
viene la yegua y a hert no le gusta no
like the mare, okay, that's why. So,
le cae bien la yegua vale por eso
well, we have been
Entonces Bueno ya llevamos ya llevamos
preparing these local people for days, as I said,
días como os digo preparando a a esta
they are people who are
gente local es gente que está
used to  work with animals and
acostumbrada a trabajar con animales y y
well there's a decision that I've made
bueno yo hay una decisión que he tomado
about how I'm going to maintain the sanctuary
de de cómo voy a mantener el santuario
but I'll probably have to do it
pero seguramente que lo tenga que hacer
from outside of Thailand okay Ah
desde fuera de Tailandia de acuerdo Ah
Wilson Ah well no that's good Wilson
Wilson Ah bueno no este bueno Wilson no
is not on Wilson's account but it's not
está en la cuenta de Wilson pero no es
Wilson okay Javi Oliveira changed the
Wilson vale Javi oliveira ha cambiado de
subject at the moment that Ler questions
tema en el momento que ler le cuestiona
Oliveira's people it's true I'll
a los de olivita es verdad ya os iré
tell you as
contando a medida que los
events unfold they're happening are
acontecimientos se van se van sucediendo
you coming or what ah that you're going after
te vienes tú o qué ah que vas detrás de
this eh as events unfold I'll
este eh a medida que los acontecimientos
go to Cani
se vayan sucediendo ya los iré em cani
Tiera okay if the campaign against Cantilla they're
tiera vale si la campaña contra cantilla
not going to believe what you want them to
no te van a creer lo que tú quieras que
believe because you say that Yuji's thing was
te crean porque digas que lo de yuji fue
a campaign okay I mean no you're not going to
una campaña vale o sea no no vas a
equate okay if the campaign against Yuji
equiparar vale si la campaña contra yuji
saying that he had already sold the savannah
diciendo que ya había vendido la sabana
without the campaign no there wouldn't have been so much
sin la campaña no no habría habido tanto
fear that all the
temor a que se vendieran en todos los
land would be sold and that's why a lot of people part of the
terrenos y de ahí mucha gente parte del
hate towards her was that she boosted
odio hacia ella fue que potenció las
donations but yes we've seen some
donaciones pero si hemos visto unos
clips of her live show with several clips
clips de su directo con varios clips
where that's where they talk and there Fran
donde es ahí donde se habla y ahí Fran
is saying that no  I'll explain
está diciendo que no os iré explicando
a little bit about how things are going but
un poquito de cómo van las cosas pero
we're preparing everything eh scenario one scenario
estamos preparando todo eh escenario uno
two scenario three because I don't
escenario dos escenario tres porque no
know how how all this is going to end
sé cómo cómo va a terminar todo esto de
okay I'm telling you I'm not going to leave
acuerdo ya os digo yo no me voy a ir de
here and leave the animals in bad
aquí y dejar a los animales en malas
conditions that's why I'm preparing
condiciones por eso que estoy preparando
all this the place was made so that the
todo esto el sitio se hizo para que los
animals can live here live peacefully and
animales vivan aquí vivan tranquilos y
in peace we have to believe the words of
en paz tenemos que creer las palabras de
a man from Fran Cuesta who has been
un señor de Fran cuesta que se ha
proven and is more than proven that he has
demostrado y está más que demostrado que
lied that he lied to save
ha mentido que ha mentido para salvar en
Yuji at the time okay very well but he
su momento a a yuji vale muy bien pero
has lied he has lied on television he has
ha mentido ha mentido en la televisión
lied on his channels he has lied to
ha mentido en sus canales ha mentido a
the public opinion as much as he
la opinión pública por mucho que él
wants to mess with the press now but
quiera ahora meterse con la prensa pero
man believe a person who really has
hombre creerte una persona que realmente
been proven to have lied about
está demostrado que ha mentido en una
such a serious thing because we're not talking about
cosa tan grave por no estamos hablando
that he lied saying it was not on
de que ha mentido diciendo no es que fue
the 20th and it was the 24th that in the end
el día 20 y fue el día 24 que al final
that's nonsense we're not talking about that
eso son tonterías no estamos hablando de
he said that she was not carrying any
que él habló que ella no llevaba ninguna
substance afterward Yes she acknowledged that
sustancia después Sí ella reconocido que
she was a consumer let's see a series of
ella era consumidora a ver una serie de
things that are very strong afterward there's
cosas que son muy fuertes después hay
another part  those that public accusation
otra parte esas ese señalamiento Público
of Franco this his wife that she's an alcoholic that
de Franco esto su mujer que alcohólica
this that that It seems to me that it's
que esto que lo otro Me parece que está
over you just said 2
fuera se acaba acabas de decir hace 2
seconds ago that she admitted to the
segundos que ella reconoció las
addictions and that he lied like he
adicciones y que él mintió como él le
makes an accusation that she's an
hace un señalamiento de que se
alcoholic that if I don't know how much if
alcohólica que si no sé cuánto si es
she's the one who brings that to light and he
ella la que saca eso a la luz y él
lies about it to protect her at what
miente en eso para protegerla en qué
point did Frank make an accusation that she
momento Frank hizo un señalamiento de
was an alcoholic of of of of
que era una alcohólica de de de de
any normal mind in the
cualquier mente normal que haya en el
world I'm really telling you and this is not
mundo de verdad os lo digo y esto ya no
about gender violence or
se trata ni de violencia de género ni
this or that no I'm not talking about
esto ni lo otro no no estoy hablando de
that I'm talking about education I'm
eso estoy hablando de Educación estoy
talking about empathy and of course believe us and
hablando de empatía y claro creernos y
now I'm going to tell you why of all
ahora os voy a decir el porqué de todo
this we believe a man who has
esto creernos a un señor que se ha
confirmed that he has lied that he has
confirmado que ha mentido que él lo ha
recognized it eh Hey that honors him yes yes yes he has
reconocido eh Oye que eso le honra si si
lied about something he has already lied in
si ha mentido en algo ya ha mentido en
everything in everything in everything in everything in everything in life
toda en todo en todo en todo en la vida
eh he has recognized that he has lied at the
eh él ha reconocido que ha mentido en su
time he lied about the Yuji issue but of
momento mintió por el tema de yuji pero
course he called the police
claro es que puso a la policía de
mafia it's that of course all this  There are
mafiosa es que claro es que todo esto
many more things behind it, it was
tiene muchas más cosas detrás hace poco
also recently invented that
se inventó también que haba han
this boxing girl had been kidnapped
secuestrado a la chica esta de box
when it was a lie as if to laugh at
cuando era mentira como para reirse de
the press which is true that I agree with
la prensa que sí que es verdad que yo
you if here nobody here
ahí te doy la razón si aquí nadie aquí
nobody makes a call nobody confirms
nadie hace una llamada nadie confirma
a news here it is published one
una noticia aquí se lo publica uno ya
after another one after another
uno va detrás de otro uno detrás de otro
and the truth is that it is absolute
y la verdad que es un auténtico
nonsense but There is information from
disparate pero Hay una información de
several days ago, information
hace ya varios días una información
on the table from several media outlets
encima de la mesa de varios medios de
where it sets off
comunicación donde hace saltar las
alarms, I am not going to say and also if you
alarmas yo no voy a decir y además si lo
see it it is with question marks and if it is all a
veis está con interrogación y si todo es
lie, people who have had
mentira a mí personas que han tenido
access to that content of
acceso a a ese contenido de de
information, to that information tell me I say
información a esa información me dicen
you are talking because everything comes out
digo tú estás hablando porque todo sale
because they call me Hey, you are talking
porque me llamama Oye tú estás hablando
about this subject like everyone is talking about
de este tema como están hablando todos
No, I have spoken two or three things on
No yo he hablado dos o tres cosillas de
Tele5 about the possibility that
tele5 de lo de la posibilidad que tiene
Yuji has of coming and such what
yuji de venir y tal lo lo que me cuenta
my deep throat tells me from Tele5 no and but I
mi garganta profunda de tele5 no y pero
am not saying more if I am not
no estoy contando más si no estoy
going into the subject the information is what
entrando en el tema la información es la
Javiel pelucas brings out. I mean, first
que saca javiel pelucas O sea primero
they tried to carry the Okay diary  and and
intentaron llevar la Okay diario y y
like Okay, diary, I mean, the media here
como Okay diario o sea aquí los medios
respects Franca a lot, you know, I mean, it
respetan mucho a franca sabes o sea
would have to be crazy for them to
tendría que ser una locura para que lo
attack him, do you understand why? Because he
atacaran me entiendes por qué porque
has the respect of many professionals,
tiene el respeto de muchos profesionales
not just in
ya no solamente de El periodismo del
film journalism, but also in the many documentaries
cine de las de un montón de documentales
that he's made, I mean, he's a person who has
que ha hecho o sea es una persona que se
earned respect for all the years he's
ha ganado el respeto por todos los años
been in what he's been doing, so then they
que lleva en lo que lleva no e entonces
come to deny that, oh, that they
pues que te vengan a desmentir que que
said it was La
ay que es que aquí dijeron que era la
Sabana because he had said it in
sabana porque él lo había dicho en
private, and I mean, it doesn't make sense, it's not
privado y O sea no tiene sentido no es
a strong thing, now another thing is that
una cosa fuerte ahora otra cosa es que
all the money collected was
todo el dinero recolectado haya sido en
based on a lie, I mean, suddenly
base a una mentira o sea de repente que
everything that we've done, Gref, me, all the
todo lo que hayamos hecho gref yo toda
people who donated to Kick, it turns out to
la gente que donó en Kick no que resulte
be a lie, that nobody was
que sea mentira que nadie le estaba
asking him for money, that the woman
pidiendo dinero que la mujer no le
wasn't asking him for money for the land
estaba pidiendo dinero para las tierras
and that we don't know what he did with that
y que no sabemos que ha hecho con ese
money, of course, then there you go,
dinero claro entonces ahí ya
uh, Okay, then there it would be very strong, of
eh Vale entonces ahí ya sería muy fuerte
course, I mean, that would be very long, you know,
claro o sea eso sería muy tocho sabes
but what we're talking about
pero es que de lo que estamos hablando
is something else that is independent.
es de otra cosa que es independiente Es
You're mixing it up, I don't know.  Why
que la estás mezclando no sé el Por qué
well I understand that Diego has a
bueno entiendo que Diego le tiene la
grudge against Fran because well Fran told him
enquina a Fran porque bueno Fran le dijo
a couple of things he doesn't tell me well it's that
un par de cosas no me dice pues es que
Diego said that's why Diego
es que Diego dijo que por eso Diego me
insulted me too and Diego sued him
insultó también y Diego lo demand
too Fran got into Diego
también Fran le se metió con Diego
because Fran got into Diego because
porque Fran se metió con Diego porque
Diego Arabal started saying that the
Diego arabal se puso a decir que de las
supermarket's security cameras didn't
cámaras de seguridad del supermercado no
look like Daniel Sancho and that he
parecía Daniel Sancho y que él que no
wasn't that he was a photographer and that wasn't Daniel Sancho
era que él era fotógrafo y que ese no
then Fran went on
era Daniel Sancho entonces Fran cogió en
a live stream and got into it with Diego so well they
un directo y se metió con con Diego
have it no then I think he
entonces pues la tienen no luego creo
asked Fran for a live stream or to
que le pidió a Fran un directo o
collaborate I don't remember something like that happened
colaborar no me acuerdo algo así pasó
but well they have their thing between them
pero bueno tiene su movida entre ellos
okay well Diego has it eh Because Fran has
vale bueno la tiene Diego eh Porque Fran
n't given him the ball many times either I
tampoco le ha dado bola muchas veces
think he mentioned it On that occasion and
creo que lo mencionó En esa ocasión y
little else Fran showed the transfers
poco más Fran mostró las transferencias
of the payment for the lands man as far
del pago de las tierras hombre hasta
as I can see a WhatsApp where
donde yo s mostró un WhatsApp donde la
Yuji told him Hey I'll leave it to you for so much
yuji le decía Oye te lo dejo en tanto
for how well you've behaved with me
por lo bien que te has portado conmigo
all my life I'll leave it to you for so much and I'll
toda la vida te lo dejo en tanto y te
transfer the lands to you and now then the thing
transfiero las tierras y ahora luego lo
about the savannah is another issue that was said
de la sabana es otro tema que se dijo
that  Fran commented privately and well
que Fran comentó por privado y Bueno
then we discussed it publicly and
pues luego lo comentamos en público y
then it turned out that it wasn't like that okay it's
luego resultó s que no era así vale se
happened Fran no no no he's doing
ha puesto Fran no no no está dando
somersaults he's not looking no no yes yes it
volteretas no está buscando no no sí sí
was like that get on topic clearly and he's
fue así ponte en el tema claro y a mí es
a very trustworthy person that was
una persona de mucha confianza a mí eso
a bit of a shock to me get on
me me resultó un poco choc le ponte en
topic and I'll tell him why and he'll tell me
el tema y le digo Por qué Y ya me cuenta
what's there I'm not going to tell him until
lo que hay yo no voy a contar hasta que
I have confirmed it whether I'm here or not
yo no lo tenga confirmado esté o no esté
and that's what I'm going to do Oh if
yo y eso es lo que voy a hacer Ah si de
suddenly I'm not here Well there will be
repente yo no estoy aquí Pues habrá
someone who will take care of him who will
alguien que lo que lo cuidará que lo
maintain him Because that was the idea I
mantendrá Porque esa erá la idea que
had with the family when we created
tenía con con la familia cuando creamos
this sanctuary look these go this way
este este santuario mira estos van por
and And that's what I want to tell you that
y Y eso es lo que os quiero comentar que
I surely if I'm not in Thailand
yo seguramente si no estoy en Tailandia
Eh well I will continue doing live broadcasts
Eh pues seguiré haciendo directos a a
through the cameras and we will continue
través de las cámaras y Seguiremos
seeing how the sanctuary is but here there
viendo cómo está el santuario pero aquí
are many possibilities there are
hay muchas posibilidades hay
possibilities that he will end up in jail There are
posibilidades de que termine la cárcel
possibilities that that I am here he
Hay posibilidades de que de que me aquí
is from Thailand and you forgot he is
es de Tailandia y se olvidaste está
looking like an ass Javi Oliveira as
quedando como el culo Javi oliveira como
always laser len giving it to the
siempre laser len dándole hasta las
gums  churra the guy insists that
encías al churra el tío insiste en que
I call him Dallas no Javi no I
yo le llamo Dallas que no Javi que no
don't call Dallas an abuser nor have I
que no le llamo a Dallas maltratador ni
called you a scammer that no matter how
a ti te he llamado estafador que por
much you and shu insist you are confusing me
mucho que tú y shu insist estáis en
with questions you are
hacerme el lío con preguntas os faltan
100 short of questions that's it anyway that they
100 ya está en fin que de que me
expel me and there is also the possibility that
expulsen y también está la posibilidad
to avoid problems Eh well I
de que para evitar problemas Eh pues
reach an agreement and I leave
llegue a un acuerdo y me voy de
Thailand okay Ah with which How is
Tailandia vale Ah con lo cual Cómo está
everyone here with which Wait
todo el mundo aquí con lo cual Espérate
pichurro that it's that I'm recording then you
pichurro que es que estoy grabando luego
pick up the phone with which well
me coges el teléfono con lo cual pues
more than anything to tell you that it's going to be
más que nada deciros eso que va a ser
one of the last walks you know that I
uno de los últimos paseos sabéis que me
always like to record the walks pass
gusta siempre grabar los paseitos pas
You go first and So I put myself between
pasa Tú primero y Así me pongo yo entre
you and the horse and that way you go calmly
tú y el caballo y así vas tranquila
come on go and and it is what it is okay it was
venga tira y y es lo que hay vale era
more than anything to tell you that there is going to be a
más que nada comentaros eso que va a
change I have to prepare everything
haber cambio tengo que preparar todo
because I can't depend on
porque yo no puedo depender de de
decisions that come from outside I
decisiones que vengan del exterior tengo
always have to look at it better for the
que siempre mirarlo mejor por los
animals I know that there is a lot of confusion now on
animales sé que hay mucho lío ahora en
the networks and stories with  nonsense but it
las redes y historias con tonterías pero
's nonsense That no, it doesn't go
que son tonterías Que no que no van a
anywhere and it's very biased and it doesn't matter
ningún sitio y están muy sesgadas y da
what's important here at the end of the
igual lo importante aquí al final del
day is that the animals are well as you
día es que los animales estén bien como
can see they are calm they live calmly and
veis están tranquilos viven tranquilos y
that is what what we want and what and what
eso es lo que lo que queremos y lo que y
we planned when we
lo que nosotros programamos cuando
created this sanctuary eh eh calm down eh calm down I'm getting confused eh calm down
creamos este santuario eh eh tranquilo
Everyone here eh calm down everyone What a shame
Todos aquí eh tranquilitos todos Qué
come on come on let me go over
pena vamos venga déjame que voy para
there Ricky Really what a shame You also
allá Ricky De verdad qué pena Tú también
have judgment soon we're not all in
tienes juicio pronto no estamos todos de
judgment Ricky wow How are we
juicio Ricky vaya tela Cómo estamos
Mochi How's life going what do you want to run
Mochi Cómo va la vida qué quieres correr
what do you want to run let's run what the
qué quieres correr vamos a correr qué
[ __ ] let's run come on let's run come on let's run come on let's run we run
[__] vamos a correr venga vamos a
so badly let's all run come on come on
corremos tan fatal vamos todos corriendo
upa what are you [ __ ] me Opa How do you like it
venga vamos upa que me coges Opa Cómo os
how do you like it pills Well here
gusta cómo os gusta pirulas Bueno aquí
is everyone here in the end
está todo el mundo aquí al final ha
everyone has come Look guys
venido todo el mundo pues Mirad chicos
everyone is here What's wrong with you
por aquí están todos Qué te pasa a ti
that you're pissed off all day long pissed off
que estás [__] todo el día [__]
since he's a son of a [ __ ] What's up girls
ya que es hijo [__] Qué pasa chavalas
Well then I said it I didn't see it well
Bueno pues lo he dicho no lo he visto
See I saw that I uploaded it but I haven't
bueno a ver He visto que lo subi pero no
seen the video guys there are going to
he visto el vídeo chavales que va a
be changes but for the animals there won't
haber cambios pero para los animales no
be changes the only thing is that
va a haber cambios lo único que
surely very soon I won't
seguramente muy pronto yo no esté aquí
agree here but This is going to continue
de acuerdo pero Esto va a seguir
working for them and if one day they
funcionando por ellos y si algún día se
have to take them away, let them take them
los tienen que llevar que se los lleven
but I'm not going to get them out of here I'm going to
pero yo no los voy a sacar de aquí voy a
fight for them until I can
pelear por ellos hasta hasta que pueda
ok that's what there is that's what there is
de acuerdo eso es lo que hay eso es lo
guys this little one is
que hay chavales este pequeñaja
used to here Okay so like I
acostumbrado aquí Bueno pues como os
told you Ah these are measures that I'm
digo Ah esto esto son medidas que yo est
involved in there measures that I have to
metido ahí medidas que yo tengo que
take Well because my responsibility is
tomar Pues porque mi responsabilidad es
for the sanctuary okay I know that many of you won't
para el santuario vale sé que muchos no
understand But the only way that
lo entenderéis Pero la única manera de
the sanctuary will continue working for
que el santuario siga funcionando para
the animals is if everything goes well with the
los animales es si todo va bien con el
issue of the trials and all this that I
tema de los juicios y todo esto que yo
leave that I'm not here look at the
me vaya que yo no esté aquí fíjate tú el
damage that has been done to Fran the turns
daño que le ha hecho a Fran los giros
of the canine you how outrageous look at how
del canino tú qué barbaridad fíjate qué
outrageous this in the end
barbaridad esto al final
and this in the end next week
e esto al final la semana que viene
something else will come out and this topic is already out you
saldrá otra cosa y este tema ya fuera
know what I'm telling you in fact I just
sabes lo que te digo de hecho me acabo
remembered dude  do you remember that yesterday
de acordar tío os acordáis que ayer
I commented on a tweet by laser len that I
comenté un tweet de laser len que os
told you I swear I hadn't seen this
dije os lo juro que no había visto esto
eh I swear I hadn't seen this eh
eh os lo juro que no había visto esto eh
Yesterday when I commented it but he sent it to me
Ayer cuando lo comenté sino que me lo
by email today F Manuel sol how
mandó por email hoy F Manuel solá cómo
you look beautiful now is when
estás guapísima ahora es cuando más
Frank will need the most the friends who
Frank necesitará de los amigos que lo
love him face with a slightly
quieren cara con el ceño ligeramente
furrowed brow a kiss character heart Today he
fruncido un beso personaje corazón Hoy
left me and I didn't go to telesalseo
se me fue y no me fui para telesalseo
because I got caught up in the space thing don't you
porque me lié con lo del space no os
remember that yesterday I commented something well I
acordáis que ayer comenté algo pues me
smell it I don't know it's my intuitions
huele no no sé es cosa mía intuiciones
from how I know them eh And how I know
de como yo los conozco eh Y de como sé
how things go I mean the serl Put that t
cómo va la vaina O sea la serl Pon ese t
yesterday not only the serl but another
ayer no solamente la serl sino que otro
hater Ah Who was it I don't remember who it
hater Ah Quién fue no me acuerdo quién
was but I saw another account with the same thing
fue pero vi a otra cuenta con lo mismo
Hey hey lada I don't know what well this is something I do
Oye oye lada no sé qué pues esto es algo
n't know what the truth is that it was a
no sé el qué la verdad yo es que fue un
topic that I didn't get involved in so well
tema en el que no me metí entonces bueno
as long as it doesn't come out for me then we'll
mientras que no me sal a mí pues lo
comment on it when it comes out but I have the
comentaremos cuando salga pero me da la
impression that  that this is the new ally
impresión de que esto es la nueva aliada
or a Win michu video or you
o bien un vídeo de Win michu o bien
know what I'm telling you or something and it's
sabes lo que te digo o bien algo y es
winged man they point to winged but I already
alada hombre señalan alada pero ya te
told you or rather I don't know what it could be eh I don't know
digo o sea no sé qué puede ser eh No sé
why the lawsuits as far as I
porque tema demandas hasta donde yo
remember Lada didn't disrespect me with
recuerdo lada no faló al respeto m con
Dallas of going out Well I don't know the plan the
Dallas de mandarse Pues no sé el plan la
truth I mean with Dallas dem going out
verdad O sea con Dallas dem mandarse
after he's hanging up posters
después de que él está colgando carteles
calling him an abuser I don't know if it makes
llamándolo maltratador no sé si si tiene
much sense But it's something out there it's
muchos sentido Pero es algo por ahí es
the next show as I call it not the
el próximo show como yo lo llamo no la
next bullet see to see every x time
próxima bala ver para ver cada x tiempo
but that I don't that I'm not here
pero que yo no que yo no está aquí
then I already tell you I have made a plan
entonces ya os digo he hecho planada
Plan B Plan C I was talking to Paloma
Plan B Plan c estaba hablando con Paloma
we have brought people to prepare it my
hemos traído gente para prepararla mi
crazy my crazy from behind eh I have
loco mi loco por atrás eh tengo gente de
support people zorro is going to be in Thailand Eh
apoyo zorro va a estar en Tailandia Eh
Well the same working for the
Pues lo mismo trabajando para el
sanctuary but here the one who has to
santuario pero aquí el que que se tiene
go is me okay Oh and making
que ir soy yo de acuerdo Ah y hacer
money on the outside well doing other
dinero por fuera pues haciendo otras
things to maintain the sanctuary is something
cosas para mantener el santuario es algo
that I already told you I created it with all the
que ya os digo yo lo creé con toda la
enthusiasm in the world for me this is it is a  a
ilusión del mundo para mí esto es es un
place of peace is the ultimatum of
un sitio de paz es el ultimátum de de la
life is happiness and I will enjoy it from the
vida es felicidad y lo disfrutaré desde
outside and I will enjoy it a lot More knowing
fuera y lo disfrutaré mucho Más sabiendo
that the animals are still here and they are still
que los animales siguen aquí y siguen
well and this is not a video Well, I would be
bien y esto no es un vídeo Bueno pues yo
happy if Fran reaches an
me alegraría si si Fran llega a un
agreement, it makes me sad that he left the
acuerdo a mí me da pena que sala del
sanctuary But well, I don't know what kind of agreement, I don't know
santuario Pero bueno no sé de qué tipo
what kind of agreement it
de acuerdo no sé qué tipo de acuerdo
could be, I mean, it could be a
podría ser o sea puede ser un acuerdo
really bad agreement, I don't know, I mean, I think that the
bien mal no sé o sea yo creo que lo
best thing would be for them to try to find an
mejor sería que intenten encontrar un
agreement in which everyone comes out
acuerdo en que en el que salgan todos
more or less well and no one comes out humiliated
bien más o menos y no salgan humillados
or harmed, no one is worth it I hope, I hope
o perjudicados ninguno vale Ojalá ojalá
But well, I don't know if it will be possible at
Pero bueno no sé yo si será posible ya a
this point
estas alturas no